You're on the phone with
your girlfriend ,she's upset.
隔窗看到你打着电话和你女友争吵
She's going off about
something that you said
她任性的拒绝了你所说的理由
Cause she doesn't, get
your humor like I do...
因为她并不像我幽默善解人意
I'm in the room
我在这个房间里
It's a typical Tuesday night
这是一个普通的周二晚上
I'm listening to the kind
of music she doesn't like
房间里充斥着和她截然相反的曲风
and she'll never know
your story like I do ...
窃喜她并不像我一样了解你
But she wears short skirts
可她穿短裙如此妖娆
I wear T-shirts
我只穿宽松T恤
She's cheer captain
她是啦啦队最璀璨的头牌
And I'm on the bleachers
而我只能在偷偷混进场内远眺你
Dreaming about the
day when you wake up
我多希望有一天你醒来之后
And find that what you're looking
for has been here the whole time
发现你所寻找的那个东西已经在你身边
If you could see that I'm
the one who understands you
如果你能有幸看到我才是那个懂你的人
been here all along
so why can't you see,
为什么你看不见我一直在这里等你
You belong with me
你知道我有多爱你
你也只能属于我
Walk in the streets with
you in your worn-out jeans
你穿着破洞牛仔裤闲庭信步
I can't help thinking
this is how it ought to be
在公园的长凳上你为我撩发时我知道你不开心
Laughing on a park
bench, thinking to myself
但我特别希望我的内心能够做点让你愉悦的事情
Hey isn't this easy
嘿这真不容易
And you've got a smile that
could light up this whole town
你的微笑照亮了我心中的整个城镇
I haven't seen it in a while
since she brought you down
自从她使你失落后我就再没见过
You say you're fine
你说你一切安好
I know you better than that
可我比她更了解你
Hey what you doing
with a girl like that
嘿你难道对这样的女孩子不心动吗
She wears high heels
她穿着高跟鞋韵味十足
I wear sneakers
我穿着运动鞋土的掉渣
She’s cheer captain and
她是啦啦队最璀璨的头牌
I'm on the bleachers
可我只能乔装打扮混入场内偷偷远眺
Dreaming about the day
when you wake up and find
我多希望有一天你醒来之后
That what you're looking for
has been here the whole time
发现你所寻找的那个东西已经在你身边
If you could see that I'm
the one who understands you
如果你能有幸看到我才是那个懂你的人
Been here all along
so why can't you see
为什么你看不见我一直在这里等你
You belong with me
你明白我多爱你
Standing by and
waiting at your back door
我站在门后偷偷等你
all this time how could
you not know Baby....
宝贝你可曾知道我倾尽心思为你所做的一切
You belong with me
你只能属于我
你知道我多爱你
Oh I remember you driving to my
house in the middle of the night
我记得你开车参加舞会的夜晚我带上了那张纸条
I'm the one who makes you laugh
当你被挫折磨砺非常难过的时候
When you know
you're about to cry
我就是那个能让你开怀大笑的人
I know your favorite songs
我知道你最喜欢的歌
And you tell me
about your dreams
你也和我敞开心扉聊了你的星辰大海
I think I know where you belong
无论你以后身处何方
I think I know it's with me.
我知道你属于我
Can't you see that I'm
the one who understands you
你无法看到我才是那个懂你的人
Been here all along
我一直在这里
So why can't you see
你为什么视而不见
You belong with me
你知道我有多爱你
Standing by waiting
at your back door
我站在门后偷偷等你
All this time
你不知道我多希望你的房间灯能亮
How could you not know
你怎么能装糊涂
Baby you belong with me
宝贝你知道我有多爱你
You belong with me
你明白我的朝思暮想
你明白我每夜的辗转反侧
Have you ever thought just maybe
看到你拿出同样的纸条，我想你也和我心有灵犀吧
you belong with me
你明白我的心心念念
You belong with me...
我要你只属于我......